<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stats Corner</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stats Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Ritchie and his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season Recap and Playoff Preview</title>
      <link>/2016/12/10/season-recap-and-playoff-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/10/season-recap-and-playoff-preview/</guid>
      <description>RIP The Jimmy G Era Even though we still have the playoffs, we’ve likely seen the end of the Jimmy G Era in Bad Newz once this season ends. RJ has the second most team names of all time, coming in at 7 in 8 seasons. Only McShane is a perfect 8 for 8 in terms of seasons/different team names. So it’s unlikely we’ll see them next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Questions Week 12</title>
      <link>/2016/11/30/taking-questions-week-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/30/taking-questions-week-12/</guid>
      <description>“In honor of my 0.3 win over RJ, what is the smallest margin of victory we’ve had since the move to decimal scoring?” Back in 2009 before we had decimal scoring we had two ties, Ready and Shokunbi tied at 97 in Week 4 then Kane and Ready tied in week 11 at 123.
In 2010 we went to decimal scoring and have had 12 games decided by less than a point, or almost two per season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Questions Week 11</title>
      <link>/2016/11/26/taking-questions-week-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/26/taking-questions-week-11/</guid>
      <description>External link to interactive post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Questions Week 10</title>
      <link>/2016/11/19/taking-questions-week-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/19/taking-questions-week-10/</guid>
      <description>Does Hartman Have a Shot at the Proportional Wins (PW) Record? Let’s take a look at the leaderboard of most PW through 10 weeks.
  Year Owner PW Through 10 Weeks PW Season Total All Time Rank    2011 Shokunbi 7.45 10.09 1  2014 Skrzyszewski 7.45 9.45 2  2013 Ready 7.18 9.18 4  2016 Hartman 7.09 NA NA  2015 Harrington 6.91 8.55 8  2009 Regan 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season Finale</title>
      <link>/2015/12/26/season-finale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/26/season-finale/</guid>
      <description>A New Points Record RJ set a new points record against Hartman in the toilet bowl semi-final. I thought he was a shoe-in for last place this year. His team stinks. But he shattered Hartman’s record against Hartman! That should teach Hartman never to set records again. So here is what the updated leaderboard looks like for most points in a game:
  Owner Team Year Week Points    Thieneman 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calm Down Tim</title>
      <link>/2015/11/12/calm-down-tim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/11/12/calm-down-tim/</guid>
      <description>Thanks Tim for the idea on the league message board for this post. I figure I’ll address it head on. For those of you who don’t know, even though to have clicked on this link you must have seen that he posted something, this is what he said:
 Can we get something on the likelihood that a team sets the single season point record and misses the playoffs?! Because it looks like we’re heading that way[.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeper Analysis</title>
      <link>/2015/09/12/keeper-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/12/keeper-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Stats Corner There are three types of owners in our league:
 The owner who is plotting his keepers before the end of the previous regular season (Regan, Ready, Harrington, Olson, D’Skae).
 The owner who starts thinking sometime during the summer who he’s going to keep (Kane, McShane, Hartman, Higdon).
 The owner who decides the morning of the draft who he’s keeping (Thieneman, Matovina).
  Whoops, I’m sorry four types:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scoring the Draft</title>
      <link>/2015/09/05/scoring-the-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/05/scoring-the-draft/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Stats Corner for the 2015 Season!
This place has a new look, a new location on the internet and new ideas. I will no longer be restricted to message board posts. Bear with me as the style evolves. Here in Week 1 I want to focus on content and content only. Future posts should have a better style.
Scoring the Draft Coming out of Draft Day I’m sure most of you were feeling pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7</title>
      <link>/2014/10/14/week-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/10/14/week-7/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a very special Stats Corner.
In light of recent emails I felt I should dedicate this week’s post to non-traditional students and the SAT. The National College Review Board has kept statistics on non-traditional students(defined as age 25+ at time of enrolment) since 1983 and…
Just kidding.
This week is special because I’m focusing not on historical game data from our database but rather the ups and downs that accompany me and likewise most of you on Sundays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6</title>
      <link>/2014/10/07/week-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/10/07/week-6/</guid>
      <description>We return to Stats Corner.
How many points does it take to win every week? We all acknowledge that it comes down to a little bit of luck. It’s whomever the schedule gods default you to year over year the same week. Take Matovina this past week. Historically he’s averaged 91.1 points per game, however he threw down 124.5 against RJ (6th highest in franchise history) but runs into the buzzsaw of RJ’s finest performance yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5</title>
      <link>/2014/09/29/week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/09/29/week-5/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Stats Corner.
I won’t try and pretend that the inspiration of this weekly Message Board Post isn’t the “Skeptical Football” column found weekly on fivethirtyeight.com. Despite its flaws it provides interesting insights into the NFL. In the inaugural column this year the author Benjamin Morris (twitter handle @skepticalsports, I reccommend you follow) created a heat map/matrix of records and historicalplayoff probabilities. Link. This week I bring that to you for Bad Newzs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4</title>
      <link>/2014/09/23/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/09/23/week-4/</guid>
      <description>A bit belated but the annual statistical update has arrived.
Note: You too can have this data. Find the game data here.If you want to play around with owner totals you’ll need to fold in the information found here. I retain all editing privileges but you can play around with the data at your leisure. I hope to update the spreadsheets weekly. In due time you will be able to find all data and R code on github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playoff Preview</title>
      <link>/1/01/01/playoff-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/01/playoff-preview/</guid>
      <description>Shout Out Congrats to Himmy Tarr, the only one to submit an answer to my trivia question last week. Jason Kidd is #2 all-time in both assists and steals. However when I wrote I had steals in mind. Nice job Tim. Also, Tim didn’t break the points record and made the playoffs. So all his fears were for naught.
 Playoff Probabilities Playoff season is here. That means another round of interpreting ESPN’s questionable tie-breaking rules, disappointments for D’Skae and Dan Ready and the #4 seed attempting to get off the schnide of having never won a first round game (it’s true).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>