<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015 on Stats Corner</title>
    <link>https://www.statscorner.com/categories/2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015 on Stats Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.statscorner.com/categories/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Season Finale</title>
      <link>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/12/26/season-finale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/12/26/season-finale/</guid>
      <description>A New Points Record RJ set a new points record against Hartman in the toilet bowl semi-final. I thought he was a shoe-in for last place this year. His team stinks. But he shattered Hartman’s record against Hartman! That should teach Hartman never to set records again. So here is what the updated leaderboard looks like for most points in a game:
  Owner Team Year Week Points    Thieneman 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playoff Preview</title>
      <link>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/12/13/playoff-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/12/13/playoff-preview/</guid>
      <description>Shout Out Congrats to Himmy Tarr, the only one to submit an answer to my trivia question last week. Jason Kidd is #2 all-time in both assists and steals. However when I wrote I had steals in mind. Nice job Tim. Also, Tim didn’t break the points record and made the playoffs. So all his fears were for naught.
 Playoff Probabilities Playoff season is here. That means another round of interpreting ESPN’s questionable tie-breaking rules, disappointments for D’Skae and Dan Ready and the #4 seed attempting to get off the schnide of having never won a first round game (it’s true).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calm Down Tim</title>
      <link>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/11/12/calm-down-tim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/11/12/calm-down-tim/</guid>
      <description>Thanks Tim for the idea on the league message board for this post. I figure I’ll address it head on. For those of you who don’t know, even though to have clicked on this link you must have seen that he posted something, this is what he said:
 Can we get something on the likelihood that a team sets the single season point record and misses the playoffs?! Because it looks like we’re heading that way[.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeper Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/09/12/keeper-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/09/12/keeper-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Stats Corner There are three types of owners in our league:
 The owner who is plotting his keepers before the end of the previous regular season (Regan, Ready, Harrington, Olson, D’Skae).
 The owner who starts thinking sometime during the summer who he’s going to keep (Kane, McShane, Hartman, Higdon).
 The owner who decides the morning of the draft who he’s keeping (Thieneman, Matovina).
  Whoops, I’m sorry four types:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scoring the Draft</title>
      <link>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/09/05/scoring-the-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.statscorner.com/2015/09/05/scoring-the-draft/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Stats Corner for the 2015 Season!
This place has a new look, a new location on the internet and new ideas. I will no longer be restricted to message board posts. Bear with me as the style evolves. Here in Week 1 I want to focus on content and content only. Future posts should have a better style.
Scoring the Draft Coming out of Draft Day I’m sure most of you were feeling pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>