<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Playoffs on Stats Corner</title>
    <link>/categories/playoffs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Playoffs on Stats Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/playoffs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Season Recap and Playoff Preview</title>
      <link>/2016/12/10/season-recap-and-playoff-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/10/season-recap-and-playoff-preview/</guid>
      <description>RIP The Jimmy G Era Even though we still have the playoffs, we’ve likely seen the end of the Jimmy G Era in Bad Newz once this season ends. RJ has the second most team names of all time, coming in at 7 in 8 seasons. Only McShane is a perfect 8 for 8 in terms of seasons/different team names. So it’s unlikely we’ll see them next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playoff Preview</title>
      <link>/2015/12/13/playoff-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/13/playoff-preview/</guid>
      <description>Shout Out Congrats to Himmy Tarr, the only one to submit an answer to my trivia question last week. Jason Kidd is #2 all-time in both assists and steals. However when I wrote I had steals in mind. Nice job Tim. Also, Tim didn’t break the points record and made the playoffs. So all his fears were for naught.
 Playoff Probabilities Playoff season is here. That means another round of interpreting ESPN’s questionable tie-breaking rules, disappointments for D’Skae and Dan Ready and the #4 seed attempting to get off the schnide of having never won a first round game (it’s true).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5</title>
      <link>/2014/09/29/week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/09/29/week-5/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Stats Corner.
I won’t try and pretend that the inspiration of this weekly Message Board Post isn’t the “Skeptical Football” column found weekly on fivethirtyeight.com. Despite its flaws it provides interesting insights into the NFL. In the inaugural column this year the author Benjamin Morris (twitter handle @skepticalsports, I reccommend you follow) created a heat map/matrix of records and historicalplayoff probabilities. Link. This week I bring that to you for Bad Newzs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>